Why do parents pay for college?
Because they think it's going to get their kids a job.
Right, and then it doesn't.
22% of them will.
Right, and so we can leverage that thing.
I mean, the good news is that the stats in that industry
only get worse, which means it's only better for you.
Our current flagship offer is called the Lunch Program.
It's a four-week, one-on-one planning service
that is priced at $4,000.
Now, we want to start a second program.
We've sold this offer one time for 30K.
I know the average cost of a year is 38K.
Right now, we're struggling with sales motion.
In the beginning, on any sales motion,
we kiss all the toads.
We kiss them all, and we figure out
who turns into princesses.
V1 is you do exactly what you're doing,
and then you just set the expectation up front,
which is, hey, we're really good at this stuff,
and so you want us to be incentivized,
and so it's 30K, and you have to pay
at least a third or half to start,
and then the rest you pay, and as soon as you get a job,
you basically continue to pay it until it's done,
and now your kid can pay it out of their side,
so you kind of future-pace it a little bit.
The other way we could do it is you could say
it's half now, half when you get,
so it's 15 now and 15 when you get the job offer.
Parent, you're gonna split it with your kid.
That way, they're gonna understand the price of this stuff,
so you're gonna pay 15, and then as soon as little Josie
gets her 70K job, we'll do the other 15K.
We'll basically plan it out off of that 70 that she's making.
She'll pay 15 the first year, and then she's done.
We believe in long-term accountability,
and part of this is you're becoming an adult now,
and you're gonna start having to pay for shit,
not mom and dad.
I'm sure mom and dad will love you saying that.
It's like they just pay for you to go to this great college,
so they're gonna front this half to get you started,
but the second half you gotta pay,
but don't worry, we're gonna set it up
as long as parents are cool with it,
and then I would just say, hey, parents,
if for some reason your kid doesn't pay,
your card's the backup card.